let API =
[
    {
        Question: "How many people on each team are in the court?",
        Options: 
        [
            "5", 
            "6", 
            "2", 
            "3"],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:" What was the original name of volleyball?",
        Options:
        [
            "Lacrosse",
            "Volley Ball",
            "Mintonette",
            "Athonome"
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"When was volleyball created",
        Options:
        [
            "2005",
            "1997",
            "1895",
            "1789",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"Who created volleyball?",
        Options:
        [
            "William G. Morgan",
            "John A. Belstrad",
            "Elijah C. Campwood",
            "Niel G. Cabaron",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"When were the first volleyball World Championships held?",
        Options:
        [
            "1949 / 1952",
            "1872 / 1918",
            "2000 / 2004",
            "1898 / 2000",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"How is the serving team chosen?",
        Options:
        [
            "A coin toss",
            "Referee's choice",
            "First team to catch the volleyball",
            "Rebound",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"What are points called in volleyball?",
        Options:
        [
            "Goals",
            "Scores",
            "Points",
            "Numbers",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"If you score a point doing a spike, what is it called?",
        Options:
        [
            "Down",
            "Score",
            "Hit",
            "Kill",
        ],
        Answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question:"What is the number of times a team can hit a ball without passing it over the net?",
        Options:
        [
            "2",
            "4",
            "3",
            "1",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"What is the player who specialises in defense called?",
        Options:
        [
            "Attacker",
            "Libero",
            "The Witcher",
            "Blocker",
        ],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:"How many sets are in a volleyball game?",
        Options:
        [
            "5",
            "3",
            "10",
            "15",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"In which way do the teams rotate?",
        Options:
        [
            "Clockwise",
            "Counter-Clockwise",
            "They not rotate",
            "active rotation",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"What is it called when a server steps past the serving line?",
        Options:
        [
            "Out of Bounds",
            "Foot Fault",
            "Out",
            "Stepping",
        ],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:"What are the names of the two volleyball referees?",
        Options:
        [
            "Forward and Backward Referee",
            "Up and Down Referee",
            "Serve and Volley Referee",
            "Referee and Flagmens",
        ],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:"Which of these is not a type of volleyball serve?",
        Options:
        [
            "Floater",
            "Underhand",
            "Tandem",
            "Hard",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"How many substitutions in a game are allowed on each team?",
        Options:
        [
            "12",
            "5",
            "7",
            "6",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
    {
        Question:"How many timeouts is a team allowed per game?",
        Options:
        [
            "4",
            "3",
            "10",
            "2",
        ],
        Answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question:"What happens when the ball lands on the line?",
        Options:
        [
            "The rally is replayed",
            "It considered 'out'",
            "It considered 'out'",
            "Deadball",
        ],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:"In what year was volleyball introduced to the Summer Olympics?",
        Options:
        [
            "2009",
            "1989",
            "1964",
            "1988",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"Who was the first person to be inducted into the Volleyball Hall of Fame?",
        Options:
        [
            "Paul Alegado",
            "Jon Stanley",
            "Ron Von Hagen",
            "William G. Morgan",
        ],
        Answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question:"Which of these is the international governing body for all forms of volleyball?",
        Options:
        [
            "NORCECA",
            "FIVB",
            "CEV",
            "PUBG",
        ],
        Answer: 1
    },
    {
        Question:"______ won the first FIVB Volleyball Men’s World Championship.",
        Options:
        [
            "Czechoslovakia",
            "The USA",
            "Japan",
            "The Soviet Union",
        ],
        Answer: 3
    },
    {
        Question:"When was beach volleyball added to the Olympics?",
        Options:
        [
            "1997",
            "1998",
            "1996",
            "1990",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"Which country won the 2022 FIVB Volleyball Women’s World Championship?",
        Options:
        [
            "Italy",
            "Brazil",
            "Serbia",
            "Philippines",
        ],
        Answer: 2
    },
    {
        Question:"Which of the following is a popular manga series about volleyball?",
        Options:
        [
            "Haikyu!!",
            "Slam Dunk",
            "Tsubasa",
            "Hentai",
        ],
        Answer: 0
    },
]


export default API